Subhan Bawany

Computer Science - IBA Karachi

Highly Organized and Friendly currently enrolled in Computer Science Degree at IBA. Nowadays, I am looking forward to internships and job opportunities in my knowledge domain. Recently I have completed my sophomore year and I want to evolve myself professionally to gain as much experience as possible. I believe in my skills and keen work ethic that keeps me dedicated to complete any task within the deadline.



Inkedin.com/in/subhan-bawany-38ba791a0

EDUCATION

Bachelor in Computer Science

Institute of Business Administration, Karachi 2019-Present CGPA: 3.60

A Levels

Beaconhouse College Program

2016-2018

Grades: 3As

O Levels

River Oaks Academy

2014-2016 Grades: 1A*, 7As and 1C

PROJECTS

- Multiclass Image Classification (AI) in Python.
- Smart Home Automation, Research Project.
- Billing System in Java.
- Sudoku Game in Java.
- Client/Server TCP and UDP in Java.

HARD SKILLS

Java Python C Language MS Excel MS Word Designing

SOFT SKILLS

Corporate Relations Collaborative Team Management Problem Solving

CERTIFICATIONS

- 1) Course on Python Google Coursera
- 2) CCNA Cisco
- 3) Introduction to Cybersecurity Cisco
- 4) Java Programming Aptech

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Quality Assurance Intern Afiniti

2020

Worked as an intern for Black Box testing software. This gave me opportunities to interact with people and enhance my communication skills.

Social Intern

Make A Wish Foundation

The work assigned to me was to fulfill the wishes for underprivileged people.

Assistant Director, Corporate Affairs And **Program Designing**

IBA Computer Science Society 2020 - Present

Served as a member of the corporate affairs and program designing. Had the experience to host one of the main events by this society named ProBattle.

Assistant Director, Content Writing

Developer Student Club(Google) - IBA 2020 - Present

Had been involved in content writing for their social media pages.

ACHIEVEMENTS

Dean's List - IBA Karachi

Was honoured to be a part of Dean's list in my third semester as I was amongst the high achievers.

Academic Based Scholarship

Got awarded with 100% scholarship on the basis of merit throughout my A Levels.